Guide to the North Carolina State University School of Design Historic Architecture Research Project Records, 1951-1976 UA 110.041
Special Collections Research Center
- UA 110.041 Series 1: Projects, 1951-1976; 32.75 linear feet 369 flat folders, 23 archival boxes, and 1 archival half box
  - North Carolina, Wake County, Raleigh: Lewis House [a.k.a. Lewis-Smith House] Field notes, photograph, negative (Box 16, Folder 283.2)
  - North Carolina, Durham County: Fairntosh Plantation Drawings, 47 drawings (Folder 284.1)
  - North Carolina, Durham County: Fairntosh Plantation Field notes (Box 16, Folder 284.2)
  - North Carolina, Durham County: Fairntosh Plantation Photographs (Box 16, Folder 284.3)
  - North Carolina, Forsyth County, Bethabara: Potters House [Gofflob-Krause House] Drawings, 11 drawings (Folder 285.1)
  - North Carolina, Forsyth County, Bethabara: Potters House [Gofflob-Krause House] Field notes, photographs, negative (Box 16, Folder 285.2)
  - North Carolina, Orange County, Chapel Hill: Old South Building, UNC Drawings, 13 drawings (Folder 286.1)
  - North Carolina, Orange County, Chapel Hill: Old South Building, UNC Field notes, photographs, negatives (Box 17, Folder 286.2)
  - North Carolina, Halifax County, Roanoke Rapids: Power Station, Mill and Aqueduct Drawings, 21 drawings (Folder 287.1)
  - North Carolina, Halifax County, Roanoke Rapids: Power Station, Mill and Aqueduct Field notes, photographs (Box 17, Folder 287.2)
  - North Carolina, Wake County, Wake Forest vicinity: Thompson House [Waterfall Plantation] Drawings [field notes missing], 12 drawings (Folder 288.1)
  - North Carolina, Hertford County, Murfreesboro: Captain Meredith House Drawings, 15 drawings (Folder 289.1)
  - North Carolina, Hertford County, Murfreesboro: Captain Meredith House Field notes, photographs, negatives (Box 17, Folder 289.2)
  - North Carolina, Carteret County, Beaufort: Mace House Drawings, 17 drawings (Folder 290.1)
  - North Carolina, Carteret County, Beaufort: Mace House Field notes (Box 17, Folder 290.2)
  - North Carolina, Cabarrus County: Jacob Stirewalt House (Mill Hill) Drawings, 13 drawings (Folder 291.1)
  - North Carolina, Cabarrus County: Jacob Stirewalt House (Mill Hill) Field notes, photographs, negative (Box 17, Folder 291.2)
  - Georgia, Wilkes County, Washington: Tupper-Barnett House Drawings, 22 drawings (Folder 292.1)
  - Georgia, Wilkes County, Washington: Tupper-Barnett House Field notes, negatives (Box 17, Folder 292.2)
  - North Carolina, Forsyth County, Winston-Salem: Wachovia Arbor Moravian Church Drawings, 9 drawings (Folder 293.1)
  - North Carolina, Forsyth County, Winston-Salem: Wachovia Arbor Moravian Church Field notes, photographs, negatives (Box 17, Folder 293.2)
  - New Jersey, Sussex County, Newton: Christ Church Rectory Drawings, 12 drawings (Folder 294.1)
  - New Jersey, Sussex County, Newton: Christ Church Rectory Field notes, photographs, negatives (Box 17, Folder 294.2)
  - North Carolina, Brunswick County, Southport: Bellamy Summer House Drawings, 19 drawings (Folder 295.1)
  - North Carolina, Brunswick County, Southport: Bellamy Summer House Field notes, photograph, negative (Box 17, Folder 295.2)
  - North Carolina, Halifax County, Halifax: St. Mark's Episcopal Church Drawings, 12 drawings (Folder 296.1)
  - North Carolina, Halifax County, Halifax: St. Mark's Episcopal Church Field notes, photograph, negatives (Box 17, Folder 296.2)
  - North Carolina, Wake County, Raleigh: Tucker House Drawings, 31 drawings (Folder 297.1)
  - North Carolina, Wake County, Raleigh: Tucker House Field notes (Box 17, Folder 297.2)
  - North Carolina, Anson County, Ansonville: All Souls Episcopal Church Drawings, 9 drawings (Folder 298.1)
  - North Carolina, Anson County, Ansonville: All Souls Episcopal Church Field notes, photograph, negative (Box 17, Folder 298.2)
  - Georgia, Calhoun County, Arlington: Davis Place Drawings, 8 drawings (Folder 299.1)
  - Georgia, Calhoun County, Arlington: Davis Place Field notes, photographs, negatives (Box 17, Folder 299.2)
  - North Carolina, Mecklenburg County, Croft: Rosedale [Johnson home] Drawings, 13 drawings (Folder 300.1)
  - North Carolina, Mecklenburg County, Croft: Rosedale [Johnson home]Field notes, photographs, negatives, 1 color slide (Box 17, Folder 300.2)
  - North Carolina, Bladen County, Tar Heel vicinity: Walnut Grove (Robeson Home) Drawings, 27 drawings (Folder 301.1)
  - North Carolina, Bladen County, Tar Heel vicinity: Walnut Grove (Robeson Home) Field notes, photographs, negatives (Box 18, Folder 301.2)
  - North Carolina, Bladen County, Tar Heel vicinity: Walnut Grove (Robeson Home) Sketches (Box 18, Folder 301.3)
  - North Carolina, Orange County, Hillsborough: Green Hill Drawings, 29 drawings (Folder 302.1)
  - North Carolina, Orange County, Hillsborough: Green Hill Field notes, photograph, negative (Box 18, Folder 302.2)
  - North Carolina, Wake County: Enno Community Drawings, 57 drawings (Folder 303.1)
  - North Carolina, Wake County: Enno Community Bethel Church field notes, photographs (Box 18, Folder 303.2)
  - North Carolina, Wake County: Enno Community Collins Farm field notes, photographs (Box 18, Folder 303.3)
  - North Carolina, Wake County: Enno Community Hollemans Store field notes, photographs (Box 18, Folder 303.4)
  - North Carolina, Wake County: Enno Community Judd House field notes, photographs (Box 18, Folder 303.5)
  - North Carolina, Wake County: Enno Community Welch House field notes, photograph (Box 18, Folder 303.6)
  - North Carolina, Wake County, Raleigh: Mann House Drawings, 13 drawings (Folder 304.1)
  - North Carolina, Wake County, Raleigh: Mann House Field notes, photograph, negative (Box 18, Folder 304.2)
  - North Carolina, Mecklenburg County, Charlotte: St. Michael and All Angels Drawings, 12 drawings (Folder 305.1)
  - North Carolina, Mecklenburg County, Charlotte: St. Michael and All Angels Field notes, photographs, negative (Box 18, Folder 305.2)
  - North Carolina, Lincoln County, Denver: Rock Springs Campground Drawings, 8 drawings (Folder 306.1)
  - North Carolina, Lincoln County, Denver: Rock Springs Campground Field notes, photographs, negative (Box 18, Folder 306.2)
  - North Carolina, Randolph County, Richland township: Williams Log Cabin Drawings, 11 drawings (Folder 307.1)
  - North Carolina, Randolph County, Richland township: Williams Log Cabin Field notes, photographs, negative (Box 19, Folder 307.2)
  - North Carolina, Caswell County, Milton: Fairview Drawings, 19 drawings (Folder 308.1)
  - North Carolina, Caswell County, Milton: Fairview Field notes (Box 19, Folder 308.2)
  - North Carolina, Carteret County, Beaufort: Potter House Drawings, 14 drawings (Folder 309.1)
  - North Carolina, Carteret County, Beaufort: Potter House Field notes, photographs, negatives (Box 19, Folder 309.2)
  - North Carolina, Wake County, Raleigh: Briggs Hardware Field notes, photographs, negative [drawings missing], 0 drawings (Box 19, Folder 310.1)
  - North Carolina, Jones County, Trenton: Grace Episcopal Church Drawings, 8 drawings (Folder 311.1)
  - North Carolina, Jones, County, Trenton: Grace Episcopal Church Field notes, photographs (Box 19, Folder 311.2)
  - Ohio, Scioto County, Portsmouth: Kinney House Drawings, 21 drawings (Folder 312.1)
  - Ohio, Scioto County, Portsmouth: Kinney House Field notes, photographs (Box 19, Folder 312.2)
  - Ohio, Scioto County, Portsmouth: Kinney House Field notes, photographs, negatives (Box 19, Folder 312.3)
  - North Carolina, Wake County, Raleigh: Seaboard R.R. Office Field notes, negatives [drawings missing], 0 drawings (Box 19, Folder 313.1)
  - Tennessee, Davidson County, Nashville: Tulip Grove Drawings, 12 drawings (Folder 314.1)
  - Tennessee, Davidson County, Nashville: Tulip Grove Field notes (Box 19, Folder 314.2)
  - Tennessee, Davidson County, Nashville: Tulip Grove Photographs, negatives (Box 19, Folder 314.3)
  - North Carolina, Brunswick County, Smith Island: U.S. Coastguard Complex Drawings, 20 drawings (Folder 315.1)
  - North Carolina, Brunswick County, Smith Island: U.S. Coastguard Complex Field notes, photographs, negatives (Box 19, Folder 315.2)
  - North Carolina, New Hanover County, Wilmington: Smith-Anderson House Drawings, 10 drawings (Folder 316.1)
  - North Carolina, New Hanover County, Wilmington: Smith-Anderson House Field notes, photographs, negative (Box 20, Folder 316.2)
  - New Jersey, Mercer County, Hopewell: Spring Hollow Farmhouse Drawings, 14 drawings (Folder 317.1)
  - New Jersey, Mercer County, Hopewell: Spring Hollow Farmhouse Field notes, photographs, negatives (Box 20, Folder 317.2)
  - North Carolina, Bertie County, Merry Hill vicinity: Scotch Hall Drawings, 19 drawings (Folder 318.1)
  - North Carolina, Bertie County, Merry Hill vicinity: Scotch Hall Field notes (Box 20, Folder 318.2)
  - North Carolina, Bertie County, Merry Hill vicinity: Scotch Hall Photographs, negatives (Box 20, Folder 318.3)
  - Maryland, Howard County, Woodbine: Farmhouse Drawings, 11 drawings (Folder 319.1)
  - Maryland, Howard County, Woodbine: Farmhouse Field notes, photograph, negative (Box 20, Folder 319.2)
  - North Carolina, Guilford County, Oak Ridge: Charles Bembow House Drawings, 11 drawings (Folder 320.1)
  - North Carolina, Guilford County, Oak Ridge: Charles Bembow House Field notes, photographs, negative (Box 20, Folder 320.2)
  - North Carolina, Gaston County, Stanley: Rhyne House Drawings, 9 drawings (Folder 321.1)
  - North Carolina, Gaston County, Stanley: Rhyne House Field notes, photographs, negatives (Box 20, Folder 321.2)
  - North Carolina, Cabarrus County, Concord: Odell House Drawings, 28 drawings (Folder 322.1)
  - North Carolina, Cabarrus County, Concord: Odell House Field notes, photographs, negatives (Box 20, Folder 322.2)
  - South Carolina, York County, Yorkville: Henry Howser House [same as project 12] Drawings, 13 drawings (Folder 323.1)
  - South Carolina, York County, Yorkville: Henry Howser House [same as project 12] Field notes, photographs, negative (Box 20, Folder 323.2)
  - North Carolina, Rockingham County, Eden: As You Like It Drawings, 11 drawings (Folder 324.1)
  - North Carolina, Rockingham County, Eden: As You Like It Field notes, photograph, negative (Box 20, Folder 324.2)
  - North Carolina, Wake County, Raleigh: Crabtree Plantation Drawings, 19 drawings (Folder 325.1)
  - North Carolina, Wake County, Raleigh: Crabtree Plantation Field notes (Box 21, Folder 325.2)
  - North Carolina, Rowan County, Salisbury: Maxwell Chambers House Drawings, 15 drawings (Folder 326.1)
  - North Carolina, Rowan County, Salisbury: Maxwell Chambers House Field notes, photographs, negatives (Box 21, Folder 326.2)
  - North Carolina, Alamance County, Mebane: Old Mebane Home Drawings, 10 drawings (Folder 327.1)
  - North Carolina, Alamance County, Mebane: Old Mebane Home Field notes, photographs, negative (Box 21, Folder 327.2)
  - North Carolina, Beaufort County: Bellefont Farm Drawings, 15 drawings (Folder 328.1)
  - North Carolina, Beaufort County: Bellefont Farm Field notes, photograph, negative (Box 21, Folder 328.2)
  - New Jersey, Union County, Union: Caldwell Parsonage Drawings, 6 drawings (Folder 329.1)
  - New Jersey, Union County, Union: Caldwell Parsonage Field notes, photograph, negative (Box 21, Folder 329.2)
  - North Carolina, Forsyth County, Winston-Salem (Old Salem): Jarrard House Drawings, 13 drawings (Folder 330.1)
  - North Carolina, Forsyth County, Winston-Salem (Old Salem): Jarrard House Field notes, photographs, negative (Box 21, Folder 330.2)
  - North Carolina, Chowan County, Edenton: Barker House Drawings, 28 drawings (Folder 331.1)
  - North Carolina, Chowan County, Edenton: Barker House Field notes, photographs, negative (Box 21, Folder 331.2)
  - North Carolina, Nash County: Tories Tavern Drawings, 16 drawings (Folder 332.1)
  - North Carolina, Nash County: Tories Tavern Field notes, photographs, negatives, 1 color slide (Box 21, Folder 332.2)
  - North Carolina, Stokes County: Moore House Drawings, 9 drawings (Folder 333.1)
  - North Carolina, Stokes County: Moore House Field notes, photographs, negatives (Box 21, Folder 333.2)
  - North Carolina, Durham County, Durham: Union Station Drawings, 24 drawings (Folder 334.1)
  - North Carolina, Durham County, Durham: Union Station Oversized sketches (Folder 334.2)
  - North Carolina, Durham County, Durham: Union Station Field notes, photographs (Box 21, Folder 334.3)
  - North Carolina, Mecklenburg County, Matthews: Providence Presbyterian Church Drawings, 15 drawings (Folder 335.1)
  - North Carolina, Mecklenburg County, Matthews: Providence Presbyterian Church Field notes, photograph, negative (Box 21, Folder 335.2)
  - North Carolina, Brunswick County, Smith Island: Baldhead Lighthouse Drawings, 9 drawings (Folder 336.1)
  - North Carolina, Brunswick County, Smith Island: Baldhead Lighthouse Field notes, photographs, negatives (Box 21, Folder 336.2)
  - North Carolina, Wake County, Raleigh: First Baptist Church Drawings, 22 drawings (Folder 337.1)
  - North Carolina, Wake County, Raleigh: First Baptist Church Field notes (Box 22, Folder 337.2)
  - North Carolina, Wake County, Raleigh: First Baptist Church Photographs (Box 22, Folder 337.3)
  - North Carolina, Chatham County, Pittsboro: Presbyterian Church Drawings, 14 drawings (Folder 338.1)
  - North Carolina, Chatham County, Pittsboro: Presbyterian Church Field notes, photograph, negative (Box 22, Folder 338.2)
  - New Jersey, Camden County: Ebenezer Hopkins House Drawings, 8 drawings (Folder 339.1)
  - New Jersey, Camden County: Ebenezer Hopkins House Field notes, photographs, negatives (Box 22, Folder 339.2)
  - North Carolina, Mecklenburg County: Coffey Log Cabin Drawings, 15 drawings (Folder 340.1)
  - North Carolina, Mecklenburg County: Coffey Log Cabin Field notes, photograph, negative (Box 22, Folder 340.2)
  - North Carolina, Wake County, Raleigh: Water Works Field notes, photographs [drawings missing], 0 drawings (Box 22, Folder 341.1)
  - North Carolina, Halifax County, Littleton: Thad Bowers House Drawings, 10 drawings (Folder 342.1)
  - North Carolina, Halifax County, Littleton: Thad Bowers House Field notes, photographs, negatives (Box 22, Folder 342.2)
  - Alabama, Lowndes County, Lowndesboro: Frazer Hall Drawings, 14 drawings (Folder 343.1)
  - Alabama, Lowndes County, Lowndesboro: Frazer Hall Field notes, photograph, negative (Box 22, Folder 343.2)
  - North Carolina, Halifax County, Scotland Neck vicinity (now moved to Halifax): Sally-Billy House Drawings, 19 drawings (Folder 344.1)
  - North Carolina, Halifax County, Scotland Neck vicinity (now moved to Halifax): Sally-Billy House Field notes, photographs, negative (Box 22, Folder 344.2)
  - North Carolina, Randolph County, Ramseur: Foust House Drawings, 11 drawings (Folder 345.1)
  - North Carolina, Randolph County, Ramseur: Foust House Field notes, photographs, negative (Box 22, Folder 345.2)
  - North Carolina, Cumberland County, Fayetteville: Cool Spring Place Drawings, 16 drawings (Folder 346.1)
  - North Carolina, Cumberland County, Fayetteville: Cool Spring Place Field notes, photographs, negatives (Box 22, Folder 346.2)
  - North Carolina, Edgecombe County, Battleboro: St. John's Episcopal Church Drawings, 13 drawings (Folder 347.1)
  - North Carolina, Edgecombe County, Battleboro: St. John's Episcopal Church Field notes, photographs, negative (Box 22, Folder 347.2)
  - North Carolina, Wake County, Raleigh: East Rock Building, St. Mary's School Drawings, 8 drawings (Folder 348.1)
  - North Carolina, Wake County, Raleigh: East Rock Building, St. Mary's School Field notes, photograph, negative (Box 23, Folder 348.2)
  - Maryland, Howard County, Ellicott City: B & O Railroad Terminal Drawings, 7 drawings (Folder 349.1)
  - Maryland, Howard County, Ellicott City: B & O Railroad Terminal Field notes, photographs, negatives (Box 23, Folder 349.2)
  - North Carolina, Mecklenburg County, Matthews: Dr. Thomas Neely Reid Home Drawings, 10 drawings (Folder 350.1)
  - North Carolina, Mecklenburg County, Matthews: Dr. Thomas Neely Reid Home Field notes, photograph, negative (Box 23, Folder 350.2)
  - Maryland, Howard County, Ellicott City: Ellicott Mills Quaker Meeting House Drawings, 8 drawings (Folder 351.1)
  - Maryland, Howard County, Ellicott City: Ellicott Mills Quaker Meeting House Field notes, photograph, negative (Box 23, Folder 351.2)
  - North Carolina, Mitchell County, Bakersville: Young Hotel Drawings, 8 drawings (Folder 352.1)
  - North Carolina, Mitchell County, Bakersville: Young Hotel Field notes, photographs (Box 23, Folder 352.2)
  - North Carolina, Beaufort County, Bath: Glebe House Drawings, 9 drawings (Folder 353.1)
  - North Carolina, Beaufort County, Bath: Glebe House Field notes, photographs, negatives (Box 23, Folder 353.2)
  - North Carolina, Wake County: Trinity Road Cottage Drawings, 6 drawings (Folder 354.1)
  - North Carolina, Wake County: Trinity Road Cottage Field notes, photograph, negative (Box 23, Folder 354.2)
  - North Carolina, Chatham County, Pittsboro: Pittsboro Masonic Lodge Drawings, 11 drawings (Folder 355.1)
  - North Carolina, Chatham County, Pittsboro: Pittsboro Masonic Lodge Field notes, photographs (Box 23, Folder 355.2)
  - Virginia, Prince George County: Merchants Hope Church Drawings, 12 drawings (Folder 356.1)
  - Virginia, Prince George County: Merchants Hope Church Field notes, photographs, negatives (Box 23, Folder 356.2)
  - New York, Suffolk County: Shelter Island Windmill Drawings, 8 drawings (Folder 357.1)
  - New York, Suffolk County: Shelter Island Windmill Field notes, photograph, negative (Box 23, Folder 357.2)
  - North Carolina, Wake County, Raleigh: Montford Hall Drawings, 20 drawings (Folder 358.1)
  - North Carolina, Wake County, Raleigh: Montford Hall Field notes, photograph (Box 23, Folder 358.2)
  - North Carolina, Wake County, Cary: Ambassador Walter Hines Page Birthplace Drawings (Folder 359.1)
  - North Carolina, Wake County, Cary: Ambassador Walter Hines Page Birthplace Field notes, photographs, negatives (Box 23, Folder 359.2)
  - North Carolina, Transylvania County: Willie Deavor Home Drawings, 18 drawings (Folder 360.1)
  - North Carolina, Transylvania County: Willie Deavor Home Field notes, photograph, negative (Box 23, Folder 360.2)
  - North Carolina, Wake County, Raleigh: William Worrell Vass House Drawings, 21 drawings (Folder 361.1)
  - North Carolina, Wake County, Raleigh: William Worrell Vass House Photographs (Box 23, Folder 361.2)
  - North Carolina, Person County, Woodsdale: Woodsdale Station Drawings (blue line prints, originals missing) [field notes missing], 4 drawings (Folder 362.1)
  - North Carolina, Hertford County: Benthall-Jenkins House Drawings [field notes missing], 7 drawings (Folder 363.1)
  - North Carolina, Wake County, Raleigh: Badger-Iredell Law Office Drawings [field notes missing], 2 drawings (Folder 364.1)
  - North Carolina, Wake County: Yates Mill-- Log Cabin Drawings [field notes missing], 2 drawings (Folder 365.1)
  - North Carolina, Guilford County, Greensboro: Blandwood Drawings [field notes missing], 6 drawings (Folder 366.1)
  - North Carolina, Chatham County: Ebenezer Church Drawings [no field notes], 2 drawings (Folder 367.1)
  - North Carolina, Hertford County, Murfreesboro: Judge David A. Barnes Home-- Outhouse Drawings [field notes missing], 2 drawings (Folder 368.1)
  - North Carolina, Mecklenburg County, Matthews: Houston (Phiefer) Home Drawings, 10 drawings (Folder 369.1)
  - North Carolina, Mecklenburg County, Matthews: Houston (Phiefer) Home Field notes, photographs, negatives (Box 23, Folder 369.2)
  - New York, Suffolk County, Smithtown: Huntting House Drawings, 12 drawings (Folder 370.1)
  - New York, Suffolk County, Smithtown: Huntting House Field notes, photographs (Box 23, Folder 370.2)
  - North Carolina, Rowan County, Rockwell: Grace Lowerstone Church Drawings, 11 drawings (Folder 371.1)
  - North Carolina, Rowan County, Rockwell: Grace Lowerstone Church Field notes, photographs, negative (Box 23, Folder 371.2)
  - North Carolina, Forsyth County, Winston-Salem (Old Salem): Salem Tavern Barn [same as project 204] Drawings, 14 drawings (Folder 372.1)
  - North Carolina, Forsyth County, Winston-Salem (Old Salem): Salem Tavern Barn [same as project 204] Field notes, photographs (Box 23, Folder 372.2)
  - Pennsylvania, York County, York: York House Drawings, 10 drawings (Folder 373.1)
  - Pennsylvania, York County, York: York House Photographs (Box 24, Folder 373.2)
  - North Carolina, Wake County, Raleigh: Executive Mansion Field notes, photographs, negatives [drawings missing (project not completed?)], 0 drawings (Box 24, Folder 374.1)
  - Projects approved not completed. Note: some projects in these folders were completed by students other than those given approval here. (Box 24, Folder 375.1)
  - Projects approved not completed. Note: some projects in these folders were completed by students other than those given approval here. (Box 24, Folder 375.2)
  - Projects approved not completed. Note: some projects in these folders were completed by students other than those given approval here. (Box 24, Folder 375.3)
- UA 110.041 Series 2: Correspondence, 1951-1972; 1.0 linear foot; 2 archival boxes
  The Historic Architecture Research Project Records correspondence series documents communications of professors in the North Carolina State University Department of Architecture, including Cecil D. Elliott, Henry L. Kamphoefner, Vernon Shogren, and Lawrence Wodehouse; with North Carolina State University architecture students; various North Carolina clerks of court; Charles E. Peterson of the National Park Service; and George S. Koyl, Moira B. Mathieson, and Earl H. Reed of the American Institute of Architects.
  - National Park Service (1958-1971, undated) (Box 24, Folder 376.1)
  - American Architectural Drawings (1963-1966) (Box 24, Folder 376.2)
  - Miscellaneous (1958-1972, undated) (Box 24, Folder 376.3)
  - Clerks of Superior Courts (1965) (Box 25, Folder 376.4)
- UA 110.041 Series 3: Course-related materials and records, 1953-1965 and undated; 0.5 Linear feet; 1 archival box
  The Historic Architecture Research Project Records course-related materials and records series includes information on ARC 300, Historic Architecture Research. Folder contents include lists of historic North Carolina buildings and lists of student projects. A 1968 student petition to have the course eliminated from the curriculum is also included, along with students' suggestions for ARC 300 modifications and alternatives.
  - ARC 300, Historic Architecture Research; Course requirements and instructions; Procedures for ARC 300, 1962 (Box 25, Folder 377.1)
  - Historic Architecture Research; Course requirements and instructions., undated (Box 25, Folder 377.2)
  - Summer Requirement: Two Weeks Regional Research Project; Course requirements and instructions, undated (Box 25, Folder 377.3)
  - Petition to change or eliminate ARC 300, with signatures and letters of support, 1968. (Box 25, Folder 377.4)
  - Annotated list of historic NC buildings (by county), 1959. (Box 25, Folder 377.5)
  - Lists of measured drawings on file, Proposed Projects for Measuring, 1958 - 1969, undated.. (Box 25, Folder 377.6)
  - Century Old Places of N.C., basic list, with 1953 addendum; Restoration Projects as Reported to Preservation of Antiquities, Inc.; List of historic NC buildings (undated handwritten manuscript), [1953?] and undated. (Box 25, Folder 377.7)
  - Student records, 1964 (Box 25, Folder 377.8)
  - Beaufort N.C., 1709, Historic Sites; Beauforts Old Buildings Become Student Project, The [Raleigh] News and Observer, 1964. (Box 25, Folder 377.9)
- UA 110.041 Series 4: Photographs, undated; 1 linear foot 3 archival card boxes